<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SNKRZ</string>
    <string name="logo_snkrz">Logo_SNKRZ</string>
    <string name="inicio_de_sesión">" Login"</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="volver_a_login">" Back to Login"</string>
    <string name="nombre">" Name"</string>
    <string name="contrasena">Password</string>
    <string name="registrarse">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="ya_tienes_cuenta">Do you already have an account?</string>
    <string name="Login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="no_tienes_cuenta">You do not have an account?</string>
    <string name="registro">Sign up</string>
    <string name="olvidaste_la_contrase_a">Forgot the password?</string>
    <string name="registrarse_mayusculas">" SIGN UP"</string>
    <string name="imagen_sneaker">Sneaker Image</string>
    <string name="repite_la_contrase_a">Repeat password</string>
    <string name="fondo_decorativo">decorative background</string>
    <string name="precio">PRICE</string>
    <string name="sneakers">SNEAKERS</string>
    <string name="grey_fog">\'GREY FOG\'</string>
    <string name="nike_dunk_lows">Nike Dunk Lows</string>
    <string name="lanzamiento">RELEASE</string>
    <string name="referencia">Reference</string>
    <string name="las_nike_dunk_originales_nacieron_realmente_en_1985_y_fueron_dise_adas_por_peter_moore_las_zapatillas_inclu_an_una_novedad_distintiva_y_es_que_llegaron_en_una_amplia_variedad_de_colores_una_caracter_stica_que_acabar_a_marcando_la_identidad_de_la_silueta">The original Nike Dunk was actually born in 1985 and was designed by Peter Moore. The shoes included a distinctive novelty, and that is that they came in a wide variety of colors, a feature that would end up marking the identity of the silhouette.</string>
    <string name="imagen_perfil">Profile picture</string>
    <string name="rectangulo_decorativo_perfil">" Decorative rectangle profile"</string>
    <string name="editar">Edit</string>
    <string name="apellido_usuario">" Last Name User"</string>
    <string name="nombre_de_usuario">" Username"</string>
    <string name="fechaEjemploSneaker">" Username"</string>
    <string name="descripcionImagenSneaker">" Sneaker Image"</string>
    <string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>
    <string name="crear_sneaker">Create Sneaker</string>
    <string name="guardar">Save</string>
    <string name="modelo_sneaker">Sneaker model</string>
    <string name="nombre_sneaker">Name Sneaker</string>
    <string name="precio_sneaker">Sneaker price</string>
    <string name="c_digo_de_referencia">Reference code</string>
    <string name="tel_fono">Phone</string>
    <string name="fecha_lanzamiento">Release Date</string>
    <string name="editar_perfil">" Edit profile"</string>
    <string name="cambiar_foto_de_perfil">Change profile picture</string>
    <string name="apellido">Last name</string>
    <string name="dni">DNI</string>
    <string name="descripci_n">Description</string>
    <string name="perfil">Profile</string>
    <string name="inicio">Start</string>
    <string name="cerrar_sesi_n">Logout</string>
    <string name="imagen_snkrz">" Snkrz Image"</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="imagen">" Image"</string>
    <string name="politicaPrivacidad">SNKRZ Privacy Policy Effective Date: [Effective Date] At SNKRZ, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and ensuring the security of the personal information they provide to us. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and protect the personal information we collect through our website and mobile applications. By using our services, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this policy. Personal Information Collected We collect personal information from our users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to: Contact Information: Name, email address, phone number, mailing address. Registration information: Username, password. Payment information: Credit or debit card details, billing information. Profile information: Personal preferences, shoe size, purchase history. Use of Information Collected We use the personal information collected for the following purposes: Process and complete purchase transactions. Personalize and improve the user experience. Send order-related information such as shipping confirmations and updates. Provide customer service and technical support. Send promotional emails and newsletters (with your express consent). Improve our products and services. Sharing Personal Information We do not sell, rent, or share personal information with third parties for their marketing purposes without your express consent. However, we may share personal information in the following circumstances: Service Providers: We work with trusted third parties to provide services such as payments, product shipping, and data analytics. These service providers have access to the personal information necessary to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Legal Compliance: We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to comply with a legal process or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SNKRZ, its users, or others. Information security We implement appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect personal information against loss, misuse and unauthorized access. However, please note that no data transmission or storage system is completely secure. Privacy Choices and Access to Personal Information You can access, correct, or delete the personal information you have provided to us at any time. If you wish to do so, please contact us using the contact details provided at the end of this policy. Cookies and Similar Technologies We use cookies and similar technologies to improve the functionality and user experience on our website and mobile applications. You can adjust the cookie settings in your web browser to manage your preferences. Changes to the Privacy Policy We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be effective as of the updated posting date on our website.</string>
    <string name="politicaprivacidad">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="a_adir_imagen">Add image</string>
    <string name="eliminar">Delate</string>
    <string name="modificar">Modify</string>
    <string name="tipoMoneda">£</string>
    <string name="_19_01_2023">19/01/2023</string>
    <string name="identificador">IDENTIFICADOR</string>
    <string name="dd1391_103">DD1391-103</string>
    <string name="gestionar_sneaker">Sneaker Manage</string>
    <string name="crear_snkrz">Create Sneakers</string>
    <string name="recuperar_contrase_a">" Recover password"</string>
</resources>